<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.plasma.cuttlefish</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.cuttlefish.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.0"/>
  <name>Cuttlefish</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Cuttlefish</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Cuttlefish</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Cuttlefish</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Cuttlefish</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Cuttlefish</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Cuttlefish</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Cuttlefish</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Cuttlefish</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxCuttlefishxx</name>
  <summary>Icon Previewer for Artists and Developers</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Vista prèvia d'icones per als artistes i desenvolupadors</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Náhled ikon pro umělce a vývojáře</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Artista eta garatzaileentzat ikono aurre-erakuslea</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Afficheur d'icônes pour les artistes et développeurs</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Pictogramviewer voor kunstenaars en ontwikkelaars</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Antevisão de Ícones para Artistas e Programadores</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Sanatçılar ve Geliştiriciler için Simge Önizleyici</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Засіб перегляду піктограм для художників та розробників</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxIcon Previewer for Artists and Developersxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Cuttlefish allows artists and developers to preview and pick icons. Cuttlefish attempts to render the icons exactly as they would look drawn in the application. It allows to filter based on category and name. Cuttlefish is not a general-purpose tool, but geared towards artists' and developers' use-cases.
        Cuttlefish also provides a plugin for Kate and KDevelop to be used as icon picker.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Cuttlefish permet als artistes i als desenvolupadors previsualitzar i seleccionar icones. El Cuttlefish intenta representar les icones exactament com es dibuixaran a l'aplicació. Permet filtrar segons la categoria i el nom. El Cuttlefish no és una eina d'utilitat general, sinó destinada als casos d'ús d'artistes i desenvolupadors. El Cuttlefish també proporciona un connector per al Kate i el KDevelop per a ser utilitzat com a selector d'icones.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Cuttlefish-ek artista eta garatzaileei ikonoak aurreikusi eta hautatzen uzten die. Cuttlefish saiatzen da ikonoak errendatzen aplikazioan marraztuta izango  luketen itxura zehatzarekin. Kategoria eta izenetan oinarrituta iragazten  uzten du. Cuttlefish ez da xede-orokorreko tresna bat, artisten eta  garatzaileen erabilera-kasuetara bideratutakoa baizik. Cuttlefish-ek gainera Kate eta KDevelope-rekin ikono hautatzaile gisa erabilia izateko plugin  bat hornitzen du.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Cuttlefish permet aux artistes et développeurs d'afficher et choisir de icônes. Cuttlefish tente de rendre les icônes exactement comme elles apparaîtraient dessinées dans l'application. Il permet un filtrage par catégorie et par nom. Cuttlefish n'est pas un outil générique, mais orienté pour les cas d'utilisation des artistes et développeurs. Cuttlefish offre aussi des modules pour Kate et KDevelop pour être utilisé pour choisir des icônes.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Cuttlefish biedt artiesten en ontwikkelaars om pictogrammen te kiezen en te bekijken. Cuttlefish probeert de pictogrammen exact weer te geven zoals ze er uit zouden zien in de toepassing. Het biedt filtering gebaseerd op categorie en naam. Cuttlefish is geen hulpmiddel voor algemeen gebruik, maar is toegespitst op gebruik door artiesten en ontwikkelaars. Cuttlefish biedt ook een plug-in voor Kate en KDevelop om te worden gebruikt als kiezer voor pictogrammen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Cuttlefish permite aos artistas e programadores fazerem uma antevisão e selecção de ícones. O Cuttlefish tenta desenhar os ícones exactamente como iriam aparecer na aplicação. Permite filtrar com base na categoria e no nome. O Cuttlefish não é uma ferramenta de uso geral, mas destinada aos casos de uso dos artistas e programadores. O Cuttlefish também oferece um 'plugin' para o Kate e KDevelop para ser usado como selector de ícones.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Cuttlefish, sanatçıların ve geliştiricilerin simgeleri önizlemesine ve seçmesine olanak tanır. Cuttlefish, simgeleri tam olarak uygulamada çizilmiş gibi görüntülemeye çalışır. Kategori ve ada göre süzme yapmanızı sağlar. Cuttlefish; genel amaçlı bir araç değil, sanatçıların ve geliştiricilerin kullanım durumlarına yöneliktir. Cuttlefish, Kate ve KDevelop'un simge seçici olarak kullanılması için bir eklenti de sağlar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Cuttlefish надає змогу художникам і розробникам попередньо переглядати і вибирати піктограми. У Cuttlefish зроблено спробу показати піктограми точно так, як вони виглядатимуть у програмі. Передбачено можливість фільтрувати списки за категорією і назвою. Cuttlefish не є інструментом загального призначення: програму призначено лише для потреб художників і розробників. У Cutlefish також передбачено додаток для Kate і KDevelop, яким можна скористатися для вибору піктограм.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxCuttlefish allows artists and developers to preview and pick icons. Cuttlefish attempts to render the icons exactly as they would look drawn in the application. It allows to filter based on category and name. Cuttlefish is not a general-purpose tool, but geared towards artists' and developers' use-cases. Cuttlefish also provides a plugin for Kate and KDevelop to be used as icon picker.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=Plasma%20SDK&amp;component=cuttlefish</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://www.kde.org/images/screenshots/cuttlefish.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <releases>
    <release version="5.25.5" date="2022-09-06"/>
    <release version="5.25.4" date="2022-08-08"/>
    <release version="5.25.3" date="2022-07-12"/>
    <release version="5.25.2" date="2022-06-28"/>
  </releases>
</component>
