<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.plasmaengineexplorer</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Plasma Engine Explorer</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Explorador de motors del Plasma</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Plasma Engine Explorer</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Moteur d'exploration Plasma</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Plasma-engine-verkenner</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Explorador de Motores do Plasma</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Gränssnittsutforskare för Plasma</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Навігатор рушіїв Плазми</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxPlasma Engine Explorerxx</name>
  <summary>Explorer for the data published by Plasma DataEngines</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Explorador de les dades publicades pels motors de dades del Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Explorer for the data published by Plasma DataEngines</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Verkenner voor de gegevens gepubliceerd door Plasma DataEngines</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Explorador dos dados publicados pelos Motores de Dados do Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Utforskare av data som publiceras av datagränssnitt i Plasma</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Навігатор для даних, оприлюднених рушієм даних Плазми</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxExplorer for the data published by Plasma DataEnginesxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Plasma Engine Explorer is a graphical tool allowing developers to test Plasma DataEngines without writing a Plasma applet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'explorador de motors del Plasma és una eina gràfica que permet als desenvolupadors provar els motors de dades Plasma sense escriure una miniaplicació Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Plasma Engine Explorer is a graphical tool allowing developers to test Plasma DataEngines without writing a Plasma applet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Plasma-engine-verkenner is een grafisch hulpmiddel die ontwikkelaars in staat stelt om Plasma DataEngines te testen zonder een Plasma-applet te schrijven.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Explorador do Motor do Plasma é uma ferramenta gráfica que permite aos programadores testarem os motores de dados do Plasma sem criar uma 'applet' do Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Gränssnittsutforskare för Plasma är ett grafiskt verktyg som låter utvecklare testa Plasma datagränssnitt utan att skriva ett Plasma miniprogram.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Навігатор рушіїв Плазми — це графічний інструмент, який надає розробникам можливість перевірити рушії Плазми без написання аплету Плазми.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxPlasma Engine Explorer is a graphical tool allowing developers to test Plasma DataEngines without writing a Plasma applet.xx</p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.plasmaengineexplorer.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=Plasma%20SDK&amp;component=engineexplorer</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>plasmaengineexplorer</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
